scancafe.com 2008-12-17

# ScanCafe - Privacy Policy

By using this website, you consent to the data practices prescribed in this statement. We may periodically make changes to this Privacy Notice that we will include on this page. Frequently reviewing this Privacy Notice and remaining informed about any changes to it is your responsibility, so we encourage you to visit this page often.

1\. **OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice to explain our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, it is made available on every page of the ScanCafe! website.

2\. **THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

Upon registration, setting up an account with ScanCafe!, we ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information which may include name, address, email address and country of residence. We use this information to establish individual accounts protected by passwords that the registered customer selects. We use the email address you provide to confirm account registration and to send notices and updates to you about the status of your order(s), our services and the site. On some pages on the site, you can order services and products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected on these pages are:

a.       Name 

b.       Address 

c.       Email address 

d.       Phone number 

e.       Credit/Debit Card Information 

f.        (etc.)

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order services and want them sent directly to other people (recipients) that you specify, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:

a.       Name 

b.       Address 

c.       Phone number 

d.       (etc.)

ScanCafe! may also automatically receive and record information on server logs from your browser. This information may include your IP address, cookie information, the pages you request, and your log in times. Cookies are pieces of information stored on a user's computer that help ScanCafe! to recognize users who return to the site and to monitor website traffic. This information may help ScanCafe! to improve the site.

**3\. THE WAY WE USE INFORMATION**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order, only to complete that order and to manage your account and keep your account current and we use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. For example, in order to ship the product and confirm delivery (shipping company) and to bill you for goods and services (transaction processor). We may disclose your personally identifiable information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

a.       conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on ScanCafe!; 

b.       protect and defend the rights or property of ScanCafe!, or; 

c.       in the event of urgent circumstances, act to protect the personal safety of users of ScanCafe!, its websites or the public.

In the event, ScanCafe! goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another entity, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, or should ever file for bankruptcy, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred.

We use the information you provide about someone else (a recipient) when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

You can register with our website if you would like to use our services and receive updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. We may use the email address you provide to us to confirm order specification, shipment delivery and to answer or ask questions associated with completing orders. We may use your contact information to contact you if we need to address questions in processing an order. We may use your contact information to occasionally send you information on our services and newsletters and, out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications.

We may send you strictly service related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt out of these communications which are not promotional in nature.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**4\. OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Unfortunately, no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect the personal information that you transmit to us, we cannot guarantee its absolute security and you do so at your own risk. ScanCafe! periodically reviews and updates security measures to continually provide improved protection for the registered customer base.

**5\. OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.

**6\. HOW YOU CAN ACCESS OR CORRECT YOUR INFORMATION**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging on to your account at ScanCafe! through the log on procedure on the website. After logging on, you can review the personally identifiable information you previously submitted, update or modify your information and then submit it. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we may also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**7\. SECURITY FOR THE PHOTOGRAPHS YOU SEND AND THE SCANS DERIVED**

To prevent misuse of your photographic images and to protect your privacy, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure your personal property. Access to your photographs is strictly controlled both physically and electronically. Your photographs and scanned images are never shared with third parties. Access is granted only to employees of ScanCafe! who are responsible for processing your images and delivering the ScanCafe! services that you request.

**8\. HOW YOU CAN CONTACT US**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us at (650) 343-0005 or send us an email at: [tc@scancafe.com](mailto:tc@scancafe.com)
